## Meron Mesfin

Midlothian, VA 23114 • mesfinm2@vcu.edu

#### **PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY**

A versatile and motivated worker blends a background in psychology and academics to offer skills in project management (CAPM), human behavior and organization. A vast level of experience from volunteering and outreach in assisting diverse groups. Brings analytical thinking, organization, and scheduling expertise to any project.

# **EDUCATION**

Southern New Hampshire University: Manchester, NH

December 2018

M.S Psychology (conc. Industrial Psychology)

Virginia Commonwealth University: Richmond, VA

May 2017

**B.S Psychology** 

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

VCU School of Nursing

February 2020 – Present

# **Departmental Administrator**

As a Departmental Administrator I am responsible for assisting faculty with any current or upcoming classes. This would include: ordering desk copies and supplies, preparing instructional materials, managing faculty webpages, and assisting with onboarding of new faculty.

Sunodía Prayer Counseling

August 2018–January 2020

# Office Manager

As an Office Manager I was responsible for planning the annual conference and quarterly seminars as well as day-to-day operations: communicating with venues, scheduling appointments, updating the website, and keeping track of finance.

### **VOLUNTEER**

American Red Cross (Volunteer) Richmond, VA

August 2019 – February 2020

#### **Blood Drive Scheduler**

• Communicate and schedule donor ambassadors for blood drives in their area

## **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

• QuickBooks, WordPress (web management), TerminalFour (web management), MailChimp, Social Media management, Typhon (< 4 months)